You brought 200,000
Are you treating me like a beggar
It's business
You ask high
And counter low
If you think one million is too little
We can negotiate
Mr. Lewes
Name your price
It's not about money
That previous special feed
laced with hormones
was produced by you right
My formula
Even if I sell it
I will sell it to an ethical company
A corrupt factory like yours
Is out of the question
Lewes
Don't be ungrateful
Calling you Mr. Lewes
Is giving you face
You really think you're a big shot
Ms. Zoe
The door is right there
See yourself out
There is nothing I want
that I cannot get
Just you wait
This Zoe
probably won't let this go easily
We will deal with whatever comes
Don't worry
By the way
The new batch of forest frogs arrives tomorrow
But the workers we hired
had some ticket issues
and won't arrive for three or four days
These next few days
will be tough on you and my parents
We are family
Why say that
How are things
with your family
I don't know
My parents aren't picking up my calls
or replying to my texts
Lewes
Daniel is a bit of a jerk
But